Hi, I'm Kathleen, I lead the careers team at Udacity.
مرحبًا أنا كاثلين، أترأس الفريق المهني في Udacity.
We support students in their job search.
ندعم الطلاب في البحث عن العمل.
The careers team knows what employers are looking for in a job candidate,
يعرف الفريق المهني ما يبحث عنه أصحاب الأعمال في المرشحين لعمل ما
and we want to work with you to market yourself as the best person for the job,
ونرغب في العمل معك لتسويقك كأفضل مرشح للعمل
whether it's a new role,
سواء كان منصب جديد
or a promotion at your current company.
أو ترقية في شركتك الحالية.
You need to be proactive in your career development to be job-ready at graduation.
ينبغي أن تكون رائدًا في تطوير مهنتك لتكون مستعدًا للعمل عند تخرجك.
For this reason, career services are available throughout your Nanodegree experience.
ولهذا السبب فإن الخدمات المهنية متاحة طوال خبرتك في مجال Nanodegree.
It's important to remember,
من المهم أن تتذكر
while you're here to learn the technical skills for a job,
أثناء تواجدك هنا لتتعلم المهارات التقنية لوظيفة ما،
it's equally important to know how to communicate
أنها بنفس أهمية معرفتك بكيفية توصيل
those skills to an employer through an application,
هذه المهارات لصاحب العمل عن طريق التطبيق،
your online profiles, and in interviews.
وملفات التعريف عبر الإنترنت وفي المُقابلات.
Let's meet the careers team who will be with you along the way.
دعونا نقابل فريقنا المهني الذي سيكون معنا طوال الطريق.
Hi I'm Rachel. Along with a network of career mentors,
مرحبًا أنا راتشل. بالاتفاق مع مجموعة من المنسقين المهنيين،
our team is here to help you from when you begin to
جاء فريقنا لمساعدتكم في معرفة من أين تبدأون البحث
look for jobs until you accept your job offer.
عن الأعمال حتى يُوافق على عرض عملك.
Career support is present at different stages throughout your Nanodegree,
يتواجد الدعم المهني في مراحل مختلفة طوال Nanodegree
and we encourage you to go through all of that
ونشجعك على خوض كل هذا
regardless of where you are in your job search.
بغض النظر عن مكانك في بحث العمل الخاص بك.
Udacity career services include guides, lessons,
تشتمل خدمات Udacity المهنية على: الإرشادات والدروس
and personalized feedback on topics like talking to recruiters,
والملاحظات الشخصية على موضوعات مثل التحدث إلى مسؤولي التوظيف
interviewing, and optimizing your online profiles.
والمقابلات، وتحسين ملفات التعريف عبر الإنترنت.
And I'm Trinh. In order to graduate career ready,
وأنا ترينه. كي تصبح خريجًا مستعدًا للحياة المهنية،
you should continuously work on your career development.
ينبغي لك العمل باستمرار على تطوير مهنتك.
Like with all learning, beginning something earlier
تتعلم كل شيء وتبدأ العمل بشكل مبكر مما
means you're more prepared when it's time to apply that learning.
يعني كونك أكثر استعدادًا عندما يحين الوقت لتُطبق ما تعلمت.
When your dream job pops up,
عندما تظهر وظيفة أحلامك،
you want to be ready for it.
ترغب في أن تكون مستعدًا لها.
We'll support you throughout your career development,
سندعمك طوال فترة التطوير المهني،
on the forums, in career coach appointments,
على المنتديات، في مواعيد المدرب المهني،
and through the career resource center.
ومن خلال مركز الموارد المهنية.
Hi I'm Kirsten, and I'm head of employer relations at Udacity.
مرحبًا أنا كريستين وأنا رئيسة العلاقات مع أصحاب العمل في Udacity.
Once you've completed the career curriculum,
بمجرد انتهائكم من المنهج المهني،
you'll be ready to apply to jobs and talk with employers.
ستصبحون على استعداد للتقدم للوظائف والتحدث إلى أصحاب العمل.
Udacity partners with industry leading companies,
تتشارك Udacity مع شركات صناعية رائدة
who are looking to hire skilled and passionate people, like you.
تبحث عن تعيين أشخاص شغوفين ومُحترفين مثلكم.
Having hiring partners means,
ومع وجود شركاء توظيف، فإن هذا يعني
you'll have direct and preferential exposure at these companies.
أنكم معرّضين مباشرة وبشكلٍ تفضيلي لهذه الشركات.
This will help give you a leg up in your job search as you explore your career options,
مما يساعدكم على اكتساب المزيد من الخبرة أثناء بحثكم عن العمل حيث أنكم ستكتشفون خياراتكم المهنية،
and develop a career path unique to you.
وتطورون مسار مهني خاص بكم.
Your passion, your location,
فضلاً عن شغفكم ومكانتكم
and other career goals.
والأهداف المهنية الأخرى.
After you complete your first core Nanodegree projects,
بعد انتهائكم من الجزء الأول من مشروعات Nanodegree،
you'll then be prompted to begin your career development with us.
سيطلب منكم بدء تطويركم المهني معنا.
We'll be there with you from then on as you explore your career options,
سنكون معكم منذ ذلك الحين وطوال اكتشافكم لاختياراتكم المهنية
and pursue your dream role. We look forward to working with you.
والسعي لتحقيق وظيفة الأحلام. نتطلع للعمل معكم.